{
    "subject": "resource/Prior_Scientific",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Cambridge",
    "human_readable": "The location of Prior Scientific is Cambridge.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9851415157318115,
            "question": "Is Prior Scientific located in Cambridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7642030715942383,
            "question": "Where is the location of Prior Scientific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6945640444755554,
            "question": "In what city is Prior Scientific situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6571806073188782,
            "question": "Where is the headquarters of Prior Scientific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6266370415687561,
            "question": "Where can you find Prior Scientific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5706321597099304,
            "question": "What is the address of Prior Scientific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5518341064453125,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of Prior Scientific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5331616997718811,
            "question": "To which city is Prior Scientific connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37781375646591187,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit Prior Scientific, where would you go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24289466440677643,
            "question": "Is Prior Scientific a global company?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of Prior Scientific is Cambridge.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6733_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you wanted to visit Prior Scientific, where would you go?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6733_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which city is Prior Scientific connected?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6733_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the geographical location of Prior Scientific?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6733_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6733_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The location of Prior Scientific is Cambridge.\" Specific mentions include Prior Scientific Instruments Ltd being an active company incorporated in Cambridge, and the company having offices in Cambridge among other locations."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}